https://highcaliberline.com/privacy-policy

Blog
Follow us on Social media:
Search:
Wristbands
24hr RushCooling / FitnessGourmet CoffeeBadgesBagsBar and BeverageBottle OpenersCarabinersClothingCooling TowelsCustom SignsDrinkwareFlashlightsGiftsGift SetsHand SanitizerKey ChainsKitchenware Lanyards Sublimation LanyardsScreen LanyardsIn Stock LanyardsWoven LanyardsEco LanyardsBottle Holder LanyardsLight UpLuggage / Bag TagsMagnetsMade in USAMicro FiberMintsNeoprene In House NeopreneOverseas NeopreneOfficePersonal CarePet CarePPE EssentialsSafety Gear Safety VestsSports & RecreationSunglassesTech and Audio Tech MobileTech ChargingTech AudioTech StandsTech MiscellaneousTools SurvivalMulti-ToolsTravelWater BottlesWriting InstrumentsWristbands
Featured
Premier Hand Sanitizer
Featured Brands >
Xtreme Closeouts >
New Items
Epoxy Dome Series
Digital Direct Printing
Covid-19 Custom Signs
All Other Closeouts
New Items New Items Mini CatalogsProduct VideosSourcingCurrent SpecialsXtreme CloseoutsUnder $1
More
PPE ProductsFulfillment ServicesMarketing Materials Create eCatalogMy eCatalogNew Item CatalogsCustomizable Catalog and FlyersMarketing CalendarFlyersOrder StatusStock CheckImprint MethodsMore
PPE ProductsMarketing MaterialsCreate eCatalogMy eCatalogNew Item CatalogsCustomizable Catalog and FlyersMarketing CalendarFlyersOrder Status
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage. We are a wholesales supplier and only do business with ASI and PPAI members.
The Information We Collect:
We do not collect information through this website. We are a business to business supplier affiliated with ASI and PPAI.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about your business when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain by making contact with us through the ASI,www.asisupplier.com , or PPAI, www.ppa.org , websites which contain telephone, mailing and email addresses for our company. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us through the ASI website, www.asisupplier.com , or the PPAI website, www.ppa.org.
About High Caliber Line
High Caliber Line offers a variety of unique promotional products perfect to meet your marketing and promotional needs. We create lasting brand recognition with our high quality imprinted and engraved products. With our new Full Caliber Color, enjoy virtually limitless possibilities when it comes to customization of multi-colored logos and personal messages. Make your next tradeshow or special event a success with customized, imprinted, innovative products by High Caliber Line. High Caliber Line, a valued supplier of promotional products, offers innovative ideas at unbeatable prices!
Company Information
About Us
HCL Blog
Privacy Policy
24 Hour Rush Policy
Shipping Policy
Sourcing
Contact Us
